We call it an order that records give to me, the model city council for Monday. July 17th 2023 but we have two
First one is Mr Becka Jim with lead agency and Tarkery Conference
Here's three minutes of up
And if you would love a meet-without conversation
Next week I'll be martin lively also with Lee Daisy
Brian will keep in 3 months so who should get telling where he was like 30 seconds later
Well, we're exactly what was rather a double thing
Over our first is after at that crowd
30 days of juncture anniversary
That's in rain and September the oldest something
I went up to doubted with great survival creeps for me
And you've got your head woke behind right there
Just to ignore what?
And you've got no clear what happened because all that thought, all the time
After at rain
The one old war of Tarkery is far back to sea
Downstream from Admiralty High was milky white
Like, I'll be with a lot of creep
All Tarky as far into the sea
The second half pile would been fly to the boat
When At Rain came all That still over
And behind the Tarkery was a very valuable part of the small one
I got dumped in Tarkery where to go
That's what we learned now
What if that concern would hold
It'd be reasonably, i.e., doing some exploring or drone
Out around the chat box
Of less difficult there is cat pile
Actors were being worked on with these 20 rows
And they had been put them out there
They're digging the chat box
There were in it back away from creeps
But no, if you thought for that, cat pile
In a quick-to'ed child was straight into Tarkery
If not, then we'd know that there is no grass
Or trees or shrubs
They are actively working on the site
Or digging into the veins of a car creek
And I could see or reach war
Seeding up from under the prison
As they try to get back
Do it with what if everybody downstream
From all the movement
Those particles
They will rush, far slowly right out again
Where's he going?
About three minutes is up
So i've told you we'll consider that
We're just going to remind everybody that we have rules set in place for a reason
And as the council are not allowed, it's interactive
So everyone is aware of why i'm here
But if you all feel passionate about this and
Everybody does what they want
Just follow on their rules
Even themselves out at jail
Thank You guys
Appreciate your comments
I got y'all there agenda for next week
All right, number three claims
So mayors and members of the council
There are a couple
Of claims on there that i would request to pull out
The claim list
One is for niece concrete
For $2191
And then another claimed for niece
Concrete
For 3759
But pulling those two out and voting on separate
And making motion we approve the claims
But pulling these two, needs claim out
Perfect
That was one
Now will improve
To play for each concrete
Are there any questions on those 2?
I'm happy to address them again or take
The amount of make a much more proof
Second
That's okay
For
For the minutes for July 3rd, 2023
Reguling
Second
Five
Presentation from Grand Gateway
Children
Mediti
Medi
Fogger
You're a close-up
Sorry
Thank you for having us tonight
I'm the new executive director for Grand Gateway
My name is Fogger, distance that February 1
And take Ed from place
Now we have a window
Ed was with us
For almost 30 years
i've been there for 26 years
I used to be executive director for 16 and half year
Before at the beginning of the executive director
It's really excited
To leave in France
It's not a much better opportunity
I think it would be good to elaborate
And first, i'm going the regime of public
In and next up at that
Whoever is 20 years old
If you have any questions
There are lots other things going on
It has transportation
Grand Opportunities
But must design something different
You've got our defined transportation grant
Yes
FDA is put out
There's like five different grants right now
And there are one that I specifically pinpoint
It has got to know in my family
If you found it, we might have turned up to find it
It isn't minimum
You're probably a pep
Over $1.5 million
But here i lost all of my community
That was not once, officially
And so it's going to be, and sometimes i'm trying
But I am still backed up
And that was supposed to be so
For a rest of my family we can get around here
Absolutely
I just could, you know, the city
You need everyone
I have no looks at me
So what are your time about eight weeks
We don't want any new things coming
I'm going to be in the end
But i come here into why
It's important that you will have a chance
Right now we're seeing our riders continue
To grow as, You know
Code is not easy for Eva
She has survived
We get through
Transit was particularly challenging to be in during
That time
So it took us three weeks
But what does that add?
Any antique backpack and contractual services
Pickback up, we can change the R numbers
Increase here in my amo
We currently have four drivers
Here is a great, please travel with some staffing
Sort of different like everyone
Working very hard on that
We just gave salary increase across to 4
And one thing i'm going do
That I would like come
Powerpoint everything is getting ready to invest
And you have, it's going be very helpful
Operationaly for probably a chance
If we've had the ability of doing something
Out-of
The call center will live and get more riders
We got new vehicles
I don't think that i haven t happened to explain
To any use as supply chain
This sort has been evolving
Amidstable before
What thing like years
In some cases
About eight months
And we're going to be out
That will really pleased with that
Other than that, i'm gonna add an example of this
I don't want every thing
So it's like the price you would go in
To powerpoint they are just coming and give us a
On call band transit
What do your hours?
Our hour is right now
Are eight or two four thirty
We have about five to ten
But those hours open for anybody?
How eight kinds of is opened to everyone
And a lot people don t think that thats sure
They could make it pretty stable
In the business with its parents
We are coping
That we will be able
To attract more rider
Ascension, these things
Absolutely open
You all can help them and travel
Any other questions?
Thanks so much, excited to hear the news
I hope you guys did a good job
If i can't speak
Thank You all
For six award lease purchase agreement
To thank your grant like for Q23-34
John Deer tractor with Diamond Boone Mower
He ever laid it
Signing and payment authority
To city manager is as he need
91,000 versus
I must have clicked around one more
It was a five
How much do you click and different bank?
Which shows him i will clicking the each one
I would like to ask all of our charges
13.0
The average person is 1100
So what size are your
I mean we are
I will say that this is actually less of a difference than the previous one
Oh, see how it can
I'll make motion to take first pass from there
Say hi
Thank you
For seven, touch check contract
18-47
Extension for fiscal year 24
248.4448
Most two proof
I
Eight
Engagement letter with all of the
Generations to conduct fiscal year 2223 audit
Motion two proof
Sorry
I
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no
No
No, we are not
We are not
10, Mayor's nomination to appoint Brandon Flutter
To the MIMA Community Facilities Authority
Replacing Bill Osborne Terms
Expire 5-1 of 28
Motioning Group
The 11. Mayor's nomination
To appoint Bethany Osborn
Public Library Board
Replicing Air and Matthew is termed expire 4
Five or 24
The group decided
Five, Mayor's nomination to appoint Justin Addis
To the MIMA Public Library Board
Replacing Becky Baird Terms expire 8-6 of 25
Motioning Group
Mayor's nominations are reappoint Sloan Marana
Do you mind about library board?
Turned up by 718 and 26
Motioning Group
Another new business of any which is the
Residence of Posting this agenda
Staff reports, 16 Mayor Council Community and Nounselmots
We got a basic couple weeks coming up
Got their root 66 rigs at
The run, truck show Coming Up
This weekend for our insider and I had a buffalo run
And it's an semi-truck Show
My car show just was semi-truck
Be the first one with that here
So we'll see how it goes
It's a bit of an adult not profit
Should be good top
They're going to do accrues, you know me?
Yep they will actually
Do 1 pass cruise down main
About their trailers
Just front, I'm gonna hit any
Any other hint against?
But well this Bboc tells me on Main Street
And then police escorting
That will be Friday evening
Probably around 7 o'clockish
There it is
Thanks for that
Anyway, they're going to do a bit of a down main
To the Bbcad Cool
As part there's no from our understay
No truck shows like this on Route 66 anywhere
So let me first one
The next six times did and then there was none at its casino
So this Bbcad will run with the cruise down Route 66
Kind of killing two birds on stone
And there'll be a big announcement
At that truck show for next year's show
That is going to bring in the rest
The CGO, see how it turns out
Of course Bbcdl run, catered to trucks
This has kind route their alley
Then we can, I hope you could see the Route66
Hareded Chessville downtown
Top of the square is coming in
A lot a little bit down
We got top to Square, Key Vanerson
The Websters, Group here
Six-foot landing
Dead metal side at Bbcad
They were, I just thought somebody was that
Whether they're concerted
Just another day
But 80s Haredman so
You'll probably see both singing and dancing
He's excited
But I hear they're really good
They've seen him multiple times
We got six-foot landing
There's a couple local guys in there, Bayon that are tall so group
The Websters show us
A few local guy on the grip here
Back with county
We always had country boys
Those guys from Jay
Good group young kids
The do-good job with some country music
Of course, Key Vanerson taught in the square
It's going to be fun
Well that should
So we'll probably find out the trucks
And then way of working on
The trucks is they go and order
But They auction off
So they did on who's first through
10th or 12th, there something in line
And that money all goes to the local charity
So it was a donation
We'll see how I go
Think of thing going
To be fun and interesting
It happened high tower had to map out
Because he didn't like throughout their hats
He changed it
Atopterity probably would
So other than that I think
That would be something else
We'll move to see managed communication
Let me take care of it
18 is on
You can just move a second
Hi
Bye